becuonlinebanking.org 2015-12-16

# 

                   IMPORTANT INFORMATION – KEEP THIS NOTICE FOR FUTURE USE
      I.       WHAT DOES BECU DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
BECU (“We”) believe that you are our most important asset. We work very hard to earn and maintain your trust. To
do that, we believe that it is absolutely vital that we protect your privacy by keeping the information we have about
you secure and confidential. While some companies may sell account holder information to others as a part of their
business strategy, BECU has not and will not follow that same practice.
We have policies and procedures in place to protect the safety of your personal and financial information. We also
have in place other physical, electronic, operational, and procedural safeguards that meet or exceed all regulations to
protect your personal and account information, which are applied equally to current and former members and
customers.
We restrict access to non-public personal information about you only to those employees and affiliated and non-
affiliated service providers: (1) to the extent necessary for the business purpose or (2) to the extent permitted by law.
This enables us to provide or offer products and services to you, process and service your accounts, and conduct our
business.
We collect the following kinds of nonpublic personal information about you:
         Information we receive from you;
         Information about your transactions with us or our affiliates;
         Information about your transactions with non-affiliated third parties; and
         Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency.
We may disclose the following kinds of nonpublic personal information about you:
         Information about you such as your name, address, social security number, assets, and income;
         Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, such as your account balance,
          payment history, parties to transactions, and credit card usage;
         Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency, such as your credit worthiness and your credit
          history.
We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to the following types of third parties (non-affiliated
third parties):
         Financial institutions with whom we have a joint marketing agreement;
         Financial service providers such as those that provide you with insurance services and investment securities
          or investment advice;
         Non-financial companies who may help us process transactions or provide customer service for your
          accounts, such as preparing or mailing statements or processing transactions;
         Credit reporting agencies;
         Service providers that provide marketing services on our behalf;
         Other companies, entities or persons, as necessary to comply with legal requirements, or as permitted by
          law.
We may disclose all of the information we collect as described above to companies that perform marketing services
on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements.
We don’t collect or disclose information about our former members to any party other than to consumer reporting
agencies or as necessary to comply with other legal requirements, or as permitted by law.
BECU 6524 11/2015

You may choose not to receive BECU or its affiliates’ marketing offers about new products and services, special
promotions and other activities we think would add value to your relationship with us. Call 1-800- 233-2328. If
you have previously chosen to opt out, and you have not since revoked that authority, you do not need to provide
another opt out at this time.
Please note that for joint account holders, we will treat an opt out direction by either account holder as applying to
the entire account.
If, at any time in the future we should decide to change any substantive part of this Privacy Statement, we will
provide you with notice of such changes.
BECU
BECU 6524 11/2015
